CURRICULUM VITAE

SUMALATHA.G. J #37, 3rd A cross, Gururaj Layout, Karthik Nagar Doddanekundi Marathahalli Post Bangalore-37

Contact no: 9071363111

Email: sumaneshambudhi@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE:

To be part of an organization which works on latest technology trends and provides challenging assignments along with opportunities to grow.

<u>Summary:</u> 6+ years experienced Talent Acquisition professional with extensive hold on working for star- up product base companies. Hands experience in End to End recruitment, Talent Acquisition, MIS Management, Vendor Management, Campus hiring.

Academic Qualification:

Msc (Computer Science): 2012 Distinction

Bachelor in HR Analytics/Dashboarding/MIS/Data Validation: AIHR Academy (Pursuing) March 2020 – March 2021

Work Experience

Avesta Computer Services Pvt. Ltd. (Deployed to Truecaller) May 2019 – Till Date

- Working as Sr. Talent Acquisition Specialist
- ➤ Point of contact for BU's for the hires as per each quarter
- > ID formulation
- Organising drives, Co- ordinating with interview panels and candidates.
- Responsible for end to end recruitment.
- Sourcing resource through job portals, referrals, head hunting.
- ➤ Working predominantly on niche skills (Focusing majorly on mid and executive level resource hiring majorly for Engineering hire)

- ➤ MIS Management: Created an MIS system to capture day to day activities of recruitment process and creating dashboard to forecast Monthly/Quarterly/ Yearly progress.
- ➤ Vendor Management: Handling 5 vendors, Screening, Shortlisting, Scheduling and sharing the update with the vendors on the candidature profiles shared

Skill2source Oct 2017-April 2019

- Working as Sr. Recruiter, Account Management and Business Development
- Responsible for end to end recruitment.
- Sourcing resource through job portals (Naukri, Monster, Times jobs, Shine, Quikr, indeed).
- ▶ Job Posting on Portals and social platforms to increase the pool of candidates.
- Sourcing Passive resource through Linkedin, Tapping Appropriate candidate through reference, Head Hunting, salary negotiation.
- > Co-ordinating with client and internal team for timely delivery of requirement.
- ➤ Handled client from IT, Manufacturing Industry, Advertising, Media, Construction,
- Lead generation
- Client acquisition.
- ➤ Worked majorly with the start up IT product base companies

Talent Lab Aug 2014-Sep 2017

- Working as Sr. Recruiter and Business Development Lead
- Responsible for Lead generation and closing the Business for generated Leads
- Screening and sourcing appropriate candidate for requirement.
- ➤ Job Posting on Portals to increase the pool of candidates
- Sourcing candidates through Job portal (Naukri, Monster, Shine, indeed, and other job Board's)
- Finding Passive resource and Business lead's through Linkedin, Tapping Appropriate candidate through reference, Head Hunting, salary negotiation.
- ➤ Handled client from IT, Manufacturing Industry, Advertising, Media, Construction, BPO, KPO domain and other verticals

With Adecco as Trainee IT Recruitment consultant since Aug 2013 - july 2014

- Working as Recruiter
- Responsible for screening and sourcing appropriate candidate for requirement.
- ➤ Job Posting on Portals to increase the pool of candidates
- ➤ Sourcing candidates through free Job portal
- Finding Passive Candidates through Linkedin, Tapping Appropriate candidate through reference, Head Hunting, salary negotiation.
- ➤ Handled IT Client HCL, HP, Cognizant, Accenture, IBM, L&T, Wells Fargo
- Major technologies handled are JAVA, Informatica, Hyperion, Sales force, UX, Mobility Solution, PHP etc confined with software development
- Minor Technologies Automation testing, Linux Virtualization, selenium, PHYTON scripting.
- Database maintenance

PERSONAL PROFILE:

Name: Sumalatha.G.J

Father Name: Jagannath.G

D.O.B: 18-11-1988

Martial status: single

Nationality: Indian

Languages known: English, Hindi, Kannada.

PERSONAL SKILLS:

- > Hard worker.
- > Target oriented.
- Comprehensive problem solving abilities.
- Clam composed ability to handle pressure.
- ➤ Ability to deal with people diplomatically.
- Willingness to learn team facilitator.

DECLARATION

I here by declare that the above mentioned details are true to the best of knowledge and hereby belief kindly do the needful and give me opportunity to work in your esteemed organisation. I have mentioned above my resume for your kind consideration and favourable orders

(SUMALATHA G.J)

DATE:

PLACE: Bangalore